<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="basketball_quotes">
        <item> "Jason Kidd: A lot of late nights in the gym, a lot of early mornings, especially when your friends are going out, you're going to the gym, those are the sacrifices that you have to make if you want to be an NBA basketball player." </item>
        <item> "Magic Johnson: Ask not what your teammates can do for you. Ask what you can do for your teammates." </item>
        <item> "Elgin Baylor: Coaching is easy. Winning is the hard part." </item>
        <item> "Michael Jordan: Even when I'm old and grey, I won't be able to play it, but I'll still love the game." </item>
        <item> "Wilt Chamberlain: Everybody pulls for David, nobody roots for Goliath." </item>
        <item> "Kobe Bryant: Everything negative — pressure, challenges - are all an opportunity for me to rise." </item>
        <item> "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar: Great players are willing to give up their own personal achievement for the achievement of the group. It enhances everybody." </item>
        <item> "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar: I can accept failure, but I can't accept not trying." </item>
        <item> "Dennis Rodman: I couldn't care less if the guy I'm guarding has HIV. I'm going to slam him anyway." </item>
        <item> "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar: I think someone should explain to the child that it's ok to make mistakes. That's how we learn. When we compete, we make mistakes." </item>
        <item> "Julius Erving: I think that my God-given physical attributes, big hands, and big feet, the way that I'm built, proportion-wise, just made basketball the most inviting sport for me to play." </item>
        <item> "Michael Jordan: Obstacles don't have to stop you. If you run into a wall, don't turn around and give up. Figure out how to climb it, go through it, or work around it." </item>
        <item> "Larry Bird: Once you are labeled the best you want to stay up there, and you can't do it by loafing around. If I don't keep changing, I'm history." </item>
        <item> "Larry Bird: Push yourself again and again. Don't give an inch until the final buzzer sounds." </item>
        <item> "Michael Jordan: Some people want it to happen, some wish it would happen, others make it happen." </item>
        <item> "Michael Jordan: Talent wins games, but teamwork and intelligence wins championships." </item>
        <item> "Michael Jordan: The game is my wife. It demands loyalty and responsibility, and it gives me back fulfillment and peace." </item>
        <item> "James Naismith: The invention of basketball was not an accident. It was developed to meet a need. Those boys simply would not play "Drop the Handkerchief."" </item>
        <item> "Jerry West: You can't get much done in life if you only work on the days when you feel good." </item>
        <item> "Michael Jordan: I would tell players to relax and never think about what's at stake. Just think about the basketball game. If you start to think about who is going to win the championship, you've lost your focus." </item>
        <item> "Charles Barkley: If you are afraid of failure you don't deserve to be successful!" </item>
        <item> "Julius Erving: If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end." </item>
        <item> "Elgin Baylor: If you look up the definition of greatness in the dictionary, it will say Michael Jordan." </item>
        <item> "Isiah Thomas: If you want consistency, then you perform. This is a performance job. You get paid to perform. Your money is guaranteed, but your minutes are not." </item>
        <item> "Larry Bird: I've got a theory that if you give 100 percent all of the time, somehow things will work out in the end." </item>
        <item> "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar: I've had enough success for two lifetimes, my success is talent put together with hard work and luck." </item>
        <item> "Michael Jordan: I've missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I've lost almost 300 games. Twenty six times, I've been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I've failed over and over and over again in my life. And that is why I succeed." </item>
        <item> "Larry Bird: Leadership is diving for a loose ball, getting the crowd involved, getting other players involved. It's being able to take it as well as dish it out. That's the only way you're going to get respect from the players." </item>
        <item> "Pete Maravich: Love never fails. Character never quits. And with patience and persistence, dreams do come true." </item>
        <item> "Shaquille O'Neal: Me shooting 40% at the foul line is just God's way to say nobody's perfect." </item>
        <item> "Isiah Thomas: My greatest gift that I have in life is basketball." </item>
        <item> "Kevin Johnson: No matter what you say, you can have as many receivers as you want; there are enough balls to go around." </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>